The store will not work correctly when cookies are disabled.

**JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.** For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.

Toggle Nav [ ](https://www.barefootbooks.com/ "Barefoot Books Logo")

Your Community Bookseller: [Firstname Lastname](#) | Your Event: Very Long Event Name Goes Here

    Sign In
    
    Login

USD

Toggle Nav

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

        * * *

    Sign In
    
    Login

USD

Basket

Search

[Search](javascript:void(0); "Search")

Search

Search

Privacy Policy

Barefoot Books Inc’s (“Barefoot Books”) Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and also help you make informed decisions when using the Barefoot Books website and services. By using or accessing our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

* * *

### What information is collected

In order to become a member of the Barefoot Books community, a user must first complete the registration process. During registration a user is required to provide their contact information (such as name, email address, and postal address) and additional psychographic data. Users are also required to provide and verify a valid email address before the account creation process can be completed.

Once established members have opted in, they will receive emails containing information regarding products, community activity, and directives from Barefoot Books from time to time. "Opted-in" means the member has approved certain emails to be sent to them from Barefoot Books, Inc.

Under rare circumstances Barefoot Books may need to contact specific or all members in order to make an important announcement about the Barefoot Books site or service changes. Members are not able to unsubscribe, or "opt-in/opt-out" of these announcements because they may contain very important information regarding their accounts. Barefoot Books reserves the right to contact members to correct account errors or to supply important information Barefoot Books deems relevant.

Please note that Barefoot Books is GDPR compliant.

#### Our Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data we store for each user session that gives you a unique ID number. We use cookies to allow us to personalize your experience on our website and to allow you to move from page to page while staying logged in to your account.

#### Log Files

We do track certain information such as type of browser and log on time for our own use. We use this information only to track from where our members may be coming and what type of software they are using. We keep this information so we can continuously improve our users' online experience and improve the Barefoot Books website. None of this information can ever be traced back to any specific person and is useful only to Barefoot Books.

#### How your information is used

We use your personally identifiable information to:

* Enable us to process transactional interactions, including purchases and Ambassador and other account registrations.
    
* Communicate with you regarding customer service questions and comments.
    
* Send you information about our products, events, levels of engagement, and more, provided that you agreed to receive these communications.
    
* Notify you of account or business errors or security issues.

We use information that is not personally identifiable to learn more about website usage and areas of our business, create more relevant marketing, and provide a better user experience.

#### Correction/Updating Personal Information

Barefoot Books users are able to change their personal information at any time through their account on the Barefoot Books website.

#### Delete your data

At any time, you can request that your account and/or your data be permanently deleted by emailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.barefootbooks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

#### Children

Barefoot Books recognizes that parents, guardians, or other adults often purchase our products for family use, including use by minors. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 for marketing purposes, but because some information is collected electronically, it can appear to be the personal information of the Barefoot Books purchaser of the product and will be treated as such under this privacy policy. If a child under 13 submits personal information to Barefoot Books and we learn that that personal information is the information of a child under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible.

### When we disclose your information

**Barefoot Books takes your privacy very seriously. Barefoot Books does not share, sell or rent your contact information.** However, there are times when it may be advantageous for Barefoot Books to make certain personal information about you available to companies that perform work for Barefoot Books. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. Also, at times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

### How we protect your information

Barefoot Books takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

Barefoot Books uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make online purchases from Barefoot Books, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it’s transmitted over the Internet.

We encourage you to take precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Among other things, change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser.

While we use both passwords and usernames to protect information online, we also take steps to protect users' information off-line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices and only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment and professionally maintained. Please keep in mind that you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information.

### How long we retain your personal information

Barefoot Books retains your information for as long as your account is active or until you request that we delete it.  

### Your rights

You have the right to the following, unless prohibited by law.

* Right to access your data: You have the right to ask for access to your data. At any time, you can request a copy of the personal data we’ve collected by emailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.barefootbooks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Any access request may be subject to a fee of $10 to cover the costs of providing the data that we hold about you.
    
* Right to update, correct or otherwise change your information: Edit your account preferences by logging in to your account at [barefootbooks.com](https://www.barefootbooks.com/), or click on “unsubscribe” in one of our emails to update your email preferences and follow the directions.
    
* Right to delete your data: Delete your data by following the instructions set forth earlier on this page.
    
* Right of all users, including California residents: Users will not be discriminated against for using any of these rights.
    
* GDPR: Barefoot Books is GDPR compliant.

### Barefoot Books Contact Details

Barefoot Books  
23 Bradford Street, 2nd Floor  
Concord, MA 01742  
United States

_Barefoot Books Customer Service_ – [\[email protected\]](https://www.barefootbooks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Toll-free: **+1.866.417.2369**, Monday to Friday, 9am-5pm EST

**We take the safety of our community seriously. To help slow the spread of COVID-19, the Barefoot Books staff is currently working remotely. Please send all queries to [\[email protected\]](https://www.barefootbooks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We appreciate your patience.**

Get a Quote for  

Customer Name

Customer Email

Phone Number

Comment

Submit

Join Our Email List!

**Newsletter**

Sign Up for Our Newsletter:

Subscribe

For customer service, email [\[email protected\]](https://www.barefootbooks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
or call +1.866.417.2369 (Mon–Fri, 9am to 5pm EST)

**Select Store**

**Store Location:**

USD

**CONNECT**  

**ABOUT**  

© 2020, Barefoot Books, Inc. All Rights Reserved.

© 2019 Barefoot Books, Inc. All rights reserved.

##### You Are Supporting

Very Long Event Name Goes Here

Hosted by: Organization Name

##### Your Community Bookseller

item(s) in basket

Checkout
